parentcircle.com 2017-03-06

# ParentCircle - Privacy Policy

We at Shri Harini Media Ltd, henceforth referred to by our property, **'ParentCircle'** ,, value your privacy and respect how you care about the way your personal information is collected, used and shared. By using or accessing our services (web, mobile or any other products of ParentCircle collectively known as ‘services’), you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy, and you hereby consent that we will collect, use, and share your information as mentioned in this policy. 

###### The information we collect

When you create an account with ParentCircle, you give us your name and email address, and create a username and password. You must provide us with accurate and complete information. You will be responsible for preserving the confidentiality of your password and for all the actions of persons accessing any of our sites through any password assigned to you. You will notify us immediately of any known or suspected unauthorized use of your account. Your user profile helps you customize your account and connect with other ParentCircle users. To help you connect with other users and to personalize your experience, we may ask you for additional information, including, but not restricted to your photo, date of birth, interests, location, contacts and DOB of children. Some of this information, such as, your name and username, will be listed publicly on our services, including in search results. Whenever you share content you see on ParentCircle via email, we may store that email address of the person, even if he/she does not have an account on ParentCircle, to send him/her email as part of our services. You may also give us permission to access your information in other services. For example, you may link your Facebook, Twitter and/or other social media accounts to ParentCircle, which allows us to obtain information from those accounts (e.g., your friends or contacts). The information we may obtain depends on your settings or privacy policies in these accounts. We may collect additional information such as your address and phone number for the purpose of enabling transactions on our website, and for purchasing/subscribing to any of our products/services. 

We receive some other information automatically when you use ParentCircle. These include: 

  * Log data, which includes your access devices’ hardware info, operating system info, your network info and location details. 
  * Similar to other websites, ParentCircle uses cookies (a small text file sent by our server to your access device each time you visit our website), to personalize your browsing experience and to maintain your session. 

###### Using your personal information

ParentCircle may use your personal information to: 

  * Administer this website 
  * Allow you to access and use our website 
  * Publish information about you on the site 
  * Publish your postings on the site for public viewing 
  * Help you connect with other users on the site 
  * Help us transact with you to send to you products that you purchase 
  * Enable us to provide you with services you subscribe to 
  * Send marketing communications to you 

###### Sharing your personal information

We may disclose any information we collect, with third parties, only after we receive your consent to do so. We may disclose non-private or non-personal information aggregated and non-personally identifiable. Any such disclosure will not include non-public, personal information regarding individual users. We employ third parties to assist us in providing and improving our services, such as without limitation, maintenance, database management and web analytics companies. Where we disclose your personal information to such third parties, they will be obligated to use such personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement. In addition to the disclosures deemed necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, ParentCircle may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights. ParentCircle may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including the information identified in this Privacy Policy, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy. 

###### Storing and securing your information

ParentCircle will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent any loss, misuse, misrepresentation or alteration of your personal information. Information that ParentCircle collects may be stored and processed in and/or transferred between any of the countries in which ParentCircle, its affiliates or service providers operate, to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy. Please note that any information that you submit for publication on the website may be published on the Internet and be available around the world. 

###### Deleting your account

If you decide to delete your account, your user profile will no longer be visible on our platform. However, we may retain your user content for a commercially reasonable period of time for backup, archival, and/or audit purposes. Furthermore, ParentCircle and its users may retain and continue to use, store, display, reproduce, re-clip, modify and distribute any of the content you have made publicly available through ParentCircle (comments, clips, clipbooks etc.). 

###### Changes to this policy

ParentCircle may update this Privacy Policy as it sees fit at any time and will post a new version on this website. You should keep checking this page to be aware of any changes to our Privacy Policy, as you will, at all times be bound by our updated policies. By continuing to use ParentCircle, you agree to accept any changes and/or updates to our policy. 

###### Linking to other websites

ParentCircle may contain links to other websites/affiliates, and is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of such parties. 

###### Contact ParentCircle

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or ParentCircle’s treatment of your personal information, please contact us at:   
Email:  contact@parentcircle.com  
Phone:  +91-44-66236623   
Address:  1st Floor, IIFL Towers, 143 MGR Salai, Kandanchavadi, Chennai 600096, TN, India.
